Guide to the Frederick Kuh papers, 1924-1967 MS2109
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Frederick Kuh papers
1924-1967
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
MS2109
19 Linear Feet
Collection contains correspondence, articles, scrapbooks of Kuh articles, speeches, diaries, writings both published and unpublished, and address and telephone books. This material dates from 1924-67. These papers are from Kuh's time as a journalist especially during World War II. Kuh was often the recipient of confidential information from numerous government officials in London and Washington, D.C.
Historical or Biographical Note
Frederick Robert Kuh (1895-1978) was born October 29, 1895 in Chicago, Illionois and died February 2, 1978, in Rockville, Md. Kuh received a PhB from the University of Chicago in 1917. Kuh, a diplomatic correspondent, was best known for his coverage of World War II. In 1942, after working for the United Press for 18 years as a correspondent throughout the world, Kuh began as the London correspondent for the Chicago Sun and continued in that role when the Sun merged with the Chicago Times. By 1952 he had been assigned to the Washington Bureau of the Chicago Sun-Times covering the State Department and foreign embassies. In his time, Kuh was considered one of the premier international reporters known especially for his many international stories including his report of Italy's impending surrender in World War II four days before it happened.
Collection Scope and Content
This collection contains correspondence, articles, scrapbooks of Kuh articles, speeches, diaries, writings both published and unpublished, and address and telephone books. This material dates from 1924-67. These papers are from Kuh's time as a journalist especially during World War II. Kuh was often the recipient of confidential information from numerous government officials in London and Washington, D.C. Some of Kuh's correspondents included Marshall Field, Edith Hoffman, James B. Reston, William Fulbright, Lyndon B. Johnson, William O. Douglas, Ralph W. Olmstead, and Konstantin G. Fedoseev. The subject files include information for various countries such as Germany, India, Switzerland, Japan, Korea, Poland, France, and subjects such as the Adolf Eichman trial, Eisenhower's visit to Europe, Kruschev's vista to the United Nations, the Japanese Peace Treaty, and the U-2 incident.
Collection note
The original paper finding aid has two indexes. These are available upon request.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Journalism; Diaries; Treaty of peace with Japan (1951); World War, 1939-1945; London (England); Scrapbooks; U-2 Incident, 1960; Washington (D.C.); Kuh, Frederick; Johnson, Lyndon B. (Lyndon Baines); Fulbright, J. William (James William); Field, Marshall; Fedoseev, Konstantin; Eisenhower, Dwight D. (Dwight David); Eichmann, Adolf; Reston, James; Chicago sun-times; Olmstead, Ralph W.; Douglas, William O. (William Orville)
- "News is Gossip", 06/14/1938-09/28/1938 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- "News is Gossip", 09/29/1938-07/15/1940 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Diaries, 07/26/1940-01/16/1942 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Diaries, 01/08/1942-11/26/1944 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Biographical Information-Clippings, Awards, Photographs, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Biographical Information-Miscellaneous, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Address and Telephone Book, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
- General Correspondence-A - K, 11/08/1929-01/12/1964 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- General Correspondence-Kulski, W.W., 07/20/1945-09/11/1955 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- General Correspondence-L - Z, 11/05/1929-10/18/1968 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Correspondence Letters from Kuh with no correspondence from addressee (chronological), 08/24/1944-05/24/1966 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Chicago Sun-Times [1/3], 1943-1963 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Chicago Sun-Times [2/3], 1943-1963 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Chicago Sun-Times [3/3], 1943-1963 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Correspondence-Atlantic Monthly, 1948-1954 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Canadian Broadcasting Corporation, 03/27/1962 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Editorial Correspondence-Chicago Sun-Times Expense Vouchers, 1955-1957 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Editorial Correspondence-Foreign Report Account Sheets [1/2], 1951-1964 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Editorial Correspondence-Foreign Report Account Sheets [2/2], 1951-1964 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Editorial Correspondence-Foreign Report, 1951-1953 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Editorial Correspondence-Foreign Report, 1954-05/1955 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Editorial Correspondence-Foreign Report, 06/1955-06/1957 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Editorial Correspondence-Foreign Report, 07/1957-10/1959 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Editorial Correspondence-Foreign Report [1/2], 11/1959-1964 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Editorial Correspondence-Foreign Report [2/2], 11/1959-1964 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Editorial Correspondence-Het Laatste Nieuws Brussels, Belgium, 08/04/1965-08/11/1965 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Editorial Correspondence-Jiji Tokyo, 1952-1964 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Editorial Correspondence-The Nation, 1952-1959 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Editorial Correspondence-Neue Zurcher Zeitung, Zurich, 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Editorial Correspondence-United Press, 1924-1941 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 1943-01/31/1944 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 01/1944 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 03/1944 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 08/1948 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 09/1948-10/1948 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 10/1948 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 11/1948 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 1949-1950 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 08/1951-09/1951 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 10/1951 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 11/1951 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 12/1951 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 01/1952 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 01/1952 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 03/1952 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 04/1952 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 05/1952 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 06/1952-07/1952 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 08/1952 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 11/1952 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 01/1953 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 01/1953 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 03/1953 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 04/1953 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 05/1953 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 06/1953 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 07/1953 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 08/1953-09/1953 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 10/1953 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 11/1953-12/1953 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 01/1954-05/1954 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 06/1954 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 07/1954 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 08/1954 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 09/1954-10/1954 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 11/1954 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 12/1954 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Chicago Sun Times-Article, 01/1955 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Chicago Sun Times-Article, 01/1955 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Chicago Sun Times-Article, 03/1955 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Chicago Sun Times-Article, 04/1955 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Chicago Sun Times-Article, 05/1955 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Chicago Sun Times-Article, 06/1955 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Chicago Sun Times-Article, 06/1955-09/1955 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Chicago Sun Times-Article, 10/1955 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 11/1955 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 12/1955 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 01/1956 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 01/1956 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 03/1956 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 04/1956 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 05/1956 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article [1/2], 06/1956 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article [2/2], 06/1956 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 07/1956 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 10/1956 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 11/1956 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 12/1956 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 01/1957 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 01/1957 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 01/1957 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 04/1957 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 05/1957 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 06/1957 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 07/1957 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 12/1957 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 01/1958 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 01/1958 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 03/1958 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 04/1958 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 05/1958 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 06/1958 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 07/1958 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 08/1958-10/1958 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 11/1958 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 12/1958 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 01/1959 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 01/1959 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 03/1959 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 04/1959 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 05/1959 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 09/1959-10/1959 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 11/1959 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 12/1959 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 01/1960 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 01/1960 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 03/1960 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 04/1960-05/1960 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 06/1960 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 07/1960-09/1960 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 10/1960-11/1960 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 12/1960 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 01/1961 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 01/1961 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 03/1961-04/1961 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 05/1961 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 06/1961 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 07/1961 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 08/1961-09/1961 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 10/1961 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 11/1961-12/1961 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 01/1962 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 01/1962 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 03/1962 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 04/1962 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 05/1962-06/1962 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 07/1962 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 10/1962 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 11/1962-12/1962 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 01/1963-01/1963 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 03/1963-04/1963 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 05/1963-06/1963 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 07/1963-08/1963 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 09/1963-10/1963 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 11/1963-12/1963 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Chicago Sun-Times Article, 01/1964-01/1964 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Foreign Report Article, 1952 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Foreign Report Article, 1953 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Foreign Report Article, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Foreign Report Article, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Foreign Report Article, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Foreign Report Article, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Foreign Report Article, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Foreign Report Article, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Foreign Report Article, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Foreign Report Article, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Foreign Report Article, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Foreign Report Article, 1963-1964 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- JIJI Article, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- JIJI Article, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- JIJI Article, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- JIJI Article, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- JIJI Article, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- JIJI Article, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- JIJI Article, 1963-1964 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Atlantic Monthly Articles, 1948-1954 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Het Laatste Nieuws (Brussels) Articles, 1965-1966 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Lerner Newspapers Articles, 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- The Nation Articles, 1952-1966 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- New Statesman and Nation Articles, 1953-1954 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Neue Zuercher Zeitung (Zurich) Articles, 1953-1954 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- New Statesman and Nation Articles, 1953-1954 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous Articles, 1942-1967 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Speech File, 1944-1961 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Speech File, 1959-1963 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Berlin Crisis, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Communist China Question-Articles, notes, and interviews, 1963-1964 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Belgrade Non-Aligned Nations-Articles, broadcasts, correspondence, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Subject Files, Conferences-Belgrade, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Subject Files, Conferences-Belgrade-Official Documents, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Subject Files, Conferences-Berlin-Foreign Ministers, 11/1953-01/1954 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Subject Files, Conferences-Bermuda-Notes, documents, printed matter, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Subject Files, Conferences-Bermuda-Articles, documents, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Subject Files, Conferences-Geneva-Articles, 05/1954 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Subject Files-Conferences-Geneva-Notes, documents, printed matter, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Subject Files-Conferences-Geneva-Foreign Ministers-Articles, Correspondence, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Subject Files-Conferences-Geneva-Articles, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Subject Files-Conferences-Nassau (Kennedy-MacMillan)-Articles, Notes, Correspondence, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Subject Files-Conferences-Paris-Foreign Ministers-Articles, Notes, Correspondence [1/2], 05/17/1949-06/22/1949 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Subject Files-Conferences-Paris-Foreign Ministers-Articles, Notes, Correspondence [2/2], 05/17/1949-06/22/1949 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Subject Files-Conferences-Paris-Schuman Plan-Articles, 11/1949 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Subject Files-Conferences-Paris Summit including U-2 affair, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Subject Files-Conventions-Democratic and Republican Presidential-Articles, press releases, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Subject Files-Conventions-Democratic-Articles, correspondence, 1956 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Subject Files-Conventions-Democratic-Articles, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Subject Files-Conventions-Republican-Articles, 1956 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Subject Files-Conventions-Republican-Articles, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Subject Files-Eichmann, Adolf Trial-Articles, correspondence, 04/07/1961-04/19/1961 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Subject Files-Eichmann, Adolf Trial-Articles, correspondence, 04/20/1961-05/05/1961 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Subject Files-Eisenhower visit to Europe-Articles, 08/10/1959-09/06/1959 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Subject Files-England-Articles, 1933 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Subject Files-Germany, East-Articles, notes (SED meetings), correspondence, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Subject Files-Germany, East-Documents, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Subject Files-Germany, East-Articles, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Subject Files-Germany, East-Notes (including interviews), printed matter, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Subject Files-Germany, East-Printed matter (background for articles), 1959 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Subject Files-Germany, West-Articles, correspondence, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Subject Files-Germany, West-Notes (including interviews), 1955 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Subject Files-Germany, West-Correspondence, notes, background publications, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Subject Files-Germany West-Background publications, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Subject Files-Germany West-Articles, correspondence, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Subject Files-Germany West-Notes, correspondence, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Subject Files-India-Articles, Correspondence, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Subject Files-India-Notes (interviews), 1957 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Subject Files-India-Notes, press releases, official documents, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Subject Files-India-Notes, documents, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Subject Files-Japan-Korea trip with Eisenhower-Articles, correspondence, 12/1952 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Subject Files-Khrushchev visit to UN-Articles, 09/14/1959-09/18/1959 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Subject Files-Poland-Clippings, documents, autographed photograph, 1954 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Subject Files-Poland-Clippings, notes, correspondence, 1954 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Subject Files-Poland-Articles, notes, 1954 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Subject Files-Poland-Correspondence, clippings [1/2], 1954 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Subject Files-Poland-Correspondence, clippings [2/2], 1954 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Subject Files-Poland-Articles, notes, correspondence, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Subject Files-Poland-Notes (including interviews), 1957 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Subject Files-Presidential Campaigns-Eisenhower-Articles, 09/05/1952-10/21/1952 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Subject Files-Presidential Campaigns-Eisenhower-Articles, 10/22/1952-11/05/1952 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Subject Files-Presidential Campaigns-Eisenhower-Articles, 10/22/1952-11/05/1952 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Subject Files-Presidential Campaigns-Stevenson, Adlai-Articles, Correspondence, 10/08/1956-10/19/1956 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Subject Files-Presidential Campaigns-Stevenson-Articles, documents, 10/20/1956-10/31/1956 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Subject Files-Switzerland-Articles, Correspondence, 09/1962 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Subject Files-USSR-Webb Miller articles, 1937 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Subject Files-United Nations-Suez, Hangarian Crises-Articles, correspondence, 11/12/1956-11/30/1956 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Subject Files-United Nations-Articles, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Subject Files-United Nations-Emergency Assembly on Mideast-Articles, correspondence, 08/12/1958-08/29/1958 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Subject Files-United Nations-Articles, correspondence, 09/05/1958-10/25/1958 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Subject Files-United Nations-Articles, correspondence, 09/05/1958-10/25/1958 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Subject Files-United Nations-Khruschev and UN-Articles, correspondence [1/2], 09/20/19608-10/13/1960 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Subject Files-United Nations-Khruschev and UN-Articles, correspondence [2/2], 09/20/19608-10/13/1960 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Subject Files-United Nations-Articles, correspondence, 12/1961 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Subject Files-United Nations-Articles, correspondence, 09/18/1962-10/06/1962 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Subject Files-United Nations-Articles, correspondence, 09/1963-10/1963 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Subject Files-United Nations-U-2 debate-Articles, correspondence, 04/1960-05/1960 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous Papers-Miscellaneous notes, 1939-1965 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous Papers-Notes on mentally retarded, 12/1965 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous Papers-Miscellaneous Notes [1/2], 1966-1967 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous Papers-Miscellaneous Notes [2/2], 1966-1967 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous Papers-Clippings of probable articles by Kuh [1/2], 1939-1958 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous Papers-Clippings of probable articles by Kuh [2/2], 1939-1958 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous Papers-US Government Press Releases [1/2], 1946-1963 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous Papers-US Government Press Releases [2/2], 1946-1963 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous Papers-Japanese Peace Treaty-Press releases, documents, clippings [1/2], 1951 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous Papers-Japanese Peace Treaty-Press releases, documents, clippings [2/2], 1951 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous Papers-Miscellaneous press releases, clippings, 1937-1958 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous Papers-Miscellaneous articles, 1965-1966 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Big Four Conference-Berlin [1/4], 01/1954-01/1954 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Big Four Conference-Berlin [2/4], 01/1954-01/1954 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Big Four Conference-Berlin [3/4], 01/1954-01/1954 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Big Four Conference-Berlin [4/4], 01/1954-01/1954 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Geneva [1/2], 04/1954-05/1954 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Geneva [2/2], 04/1954-05/1954 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- "Spotlight On West Germany's Election", 09/16/1957 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- India [1/4], 11/1957-12/1957 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- India [2/4], 11/1957-12/1957 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- India [3/4], 11/1957-12/1957 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- India [4/4], 11/1957-12/1957 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Geneva [1/2], 07/1955 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Geneva [2/2], 07/1955 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- West Germany [1/2], 1957 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- West Germany [2/2], 1957 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- West Germany, 1953 ca. (Box 35, Folder 3)
- NATO-Notes, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Poland [1/2], 1954 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Poland [2/2], 1954 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Scrapbook-Newspaper clippings, 10/01/1943-05/11/1945 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Scrapbook-Newspaper clippings, 05/12/1945-03/20/1948 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Scrapbook-Newspaper Clippings, 1947 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Scrapbook-Newspaper Clippings, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Scrapbook-Newspaper Clippings, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Papers, undated (Box 38)
  General note
  This appears to be an index created by GW staff. It may be primarily for the diaries.
- Index Cards A-Ca and Ca-Ei, undated (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Index Cards El-Hea and He-Ka, undated (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Index Cards Kh-Mas and Mat-Pri, undated (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Index Cards Prit-Sim, undated (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Index Cards Sin-Von, undated (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Index Cards Vor-Z, undated (Box 38, Folder 6)
- The French Defense Effort, 10/1952 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Governmental Measures Affecting Investment in India, 07/1950 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Life And Death Of A Spy Chief, 09/1952 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Report Of The Indian Delegation To China, 07/1956-08/1956 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- International Peasant Union, 01/1956 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- NATO The First Five Years, 1949-1954 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Evolution in Jugoslavia, 07/1956 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Egypt And The West [1/2], 09/1956 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Egypt And The West [2/2], 09/1956 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- America In The World Today, 01/27/1957 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Our Stake in The World Today, 07/1954-08/1954 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- The Northern Islands, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Look Magazine, 08/25/1964 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Poland of To-day, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 14)
- Communist Perspective, undated (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Britain's Economic Problem And It's Meaning For America, 03/01/1953 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Britain In Brief, 12/1952 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- International Economic Survey, 01/1956 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- International Trade Policy Issues, 01/1953 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- British Affairs, 06/1957 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Labor and Industry In Britain, 03/1956 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- The Future Of The Ryukyus, 07/1953 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Austria: A Summary of Facts and Figures, 1953 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Bonn Bereitet Revanchekrieg Vor, undated (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Steps To Peace: A Quaker View Of U.S. Foreign Policy, 1951 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Speak Truth To Power, undated (Box 40, Folder 12)